&gt;&gt; At this point, you've built and trained deep neural networks from the ground up.
&gt;&gt; これまでにディープニューラルネットワークをゼロから構築し トレーニングしました
Congratulations. This is an amazing set of skills with a wide range of applications.
おめでとうございます  これは幅広く応用できる素晴らしいスキルセットです
However, deep learning engineers often don't actually
ただし ディープラーニングエンジニアがニューラルネットワークを
start with a blank slate when they're building neural networks.
構築するとき 白紙から始めることはあまりありません
&gt;&gt; Starting from scratch can be time-consuming.
&gt;&gt; ゼロから始めるのは時間がかかりますからね
It's not just architecting the network,
ネットワークを構築するだけでなく
but also experimenting with it,
実験して
training it and adjusting it,
トレーニングして 調整するには
which can take days or even weeks.
何日も 何週間もかかることがあります
To accelerate the process,
このプロセスを加速するために
engineers often begin with a pre-trained network and then modify it.
エンジニアはトレーニング済みのネットワークから始めて 修正を加えます
&gt;&gt; Fine-tuning an existing network is a powerful technique because
&gt;&gt; 既存のネットワークの微調整はパワフルな技法です
improving a network takes much less effort than creating one from scratch.
ゼロから作成するより はるかに少ない労力でネットワークを改善できます
Going even further, we can take an existing network
さらに言えば 既存のネットワークを
and re-purpose it for a related but different task.
関連はあるが別のタスクのために利用することもできます
Re-purposing a network is called Transfer Learning,
別の目的でのネットワークの再利用は転移学習と呼ばれます
because you're transferring the learning from an existing network to a new one.
既存のネットワークから新しいネットワークへ学習を転移するからです
&gt;&gt; To learn more about why Transfer Learning
&gt;&gt; 転移学習がディープニューラルネットワークの
is so important for building deep neural networks,
構築にとって非常に重要な理由を詳しく学ぶために
we're going to get some advice from Bryan Cantanzaro,
Bryan Cantanzaroからアドバイスをもらうことにします
a deep learning expert in NVIDIA.
彼はNVIDIAのディープラーニングのエキスパートです